Previously on This Is Us...
《我们的生活》前情提要
I love our life.
我喜欢我们的生活
I love it right now.
就喜欢现在的生活
And I'm so scared of changing it.
我很怕会有改变
I'm not gonna stand for anything changing between us.
我无法容忍我们之间有任何改变
I don't want to be different from them.
我不想和他们不一样
Different from who? Who, the kids at school?
和谁不一样  学校里那些孩子吗
If I get an "A," I'll get ice cream,
如果得了A  我就有冰激凌吃
and Kate and Kevin won't, and then they'll hate me.
而凯特和凯文没有  他们会恨我的
I can't fall for a fat person right now.
我现在可不能和一个胖子谈恋爱
I guess I'll lose the weight then.
那看来我得减肥了
What did I do to deserve this?
我做了什么能享受这种待遇呢
You've done a lot of really nice things for me,
你为我做了太多贴心的事
so I wand to return the favor.
所以我想回报你
By cutting up cardboard into little squares
把"硬纸板"切成方块  放到碗里
and putting it in a bowl? Yum.
来回报我吗  "美味啊"
Hey, so, Kevin, uh, it's been a few days now, you know,
凯文  自从那天你过来
since you showed up.
就一直住在这里
- Without calling. - Right.
-也没提前打电话  -对
I was just sort of wondering...
就是想问下...
When are you leaving?
你什么时候走
Yeah.
就这意思
Washing machine is officially cooked.
洗衣机这下真是不行了
Ah, she's still got some life in her, at least six more cycles.
不  她还能用呢  至少还能洗六轮
Jack, we have three infants.
杰克  我们家有三个孩子
We're gonna be doing six cycles by noon.
中午之前就能洗六回了
- Jack? - Yeah.
-杰克  -干嘛
Uh, I need your help.
快来帮忙
It's leaking everywhere.
水漏得到处都是
This is bail out!
终于解脱了
Oh, my God.
天啊
This is the best washing machine in the entire world.
这是全世界最好的洗衣机
I'm actually turned on by this washing machine.
这台洗衣机真让我兴奋
I'm gonna show you turned on.
我来告诉你什么叫"性奋"
- Oh, you are? - I am.
-真的吗  -当然
- Big Three! - Big Three!
-三个小家伙  -三个小家伙
I just want to do a small kitchen remodel.
我只是想把厨房稍微改动一下
Just some new cabinets, maybe some new countertops.
换几个新橱柜  再把工作台面换了
给我  兰德尔  那是我的弹力球[蛋蛋]Give me those, Randall, they're my bouncy balls.
But Mom gave them to me.
但是[屁股]妈妈把球给我了
You said "butt."
你说了"屁股"
You said "balls."
你说了"蛋蛋"
What the hell, Kevin?
你干什么  凯文
Turn the lights out, man, it's 2:00 A.M.
把灯关了  现在都凌晨两点了
Damn it, Kevin, you ruined it.
该死  凯文  你把它给毁了
It's all ruined.
都被你给毁了
Hey, man, I'm...
兄弟  我...
I'm sorry, dude.
对不起  伙计
Don't.
别
What are you doing?
你在干什么
I'm trying to help you.
我是想帮你
Look, I'm sorry I touched your precious woobie.
对不起我碰了你珍贵的毯子
That thing reeks by the way.
可它也太臭了
It's the blanket I was left in, Kevin.
这是我被遗弃时裹着的毯子  凯文
Well, it doesn't mean you can't wash it once in a while.
那也不代表你不能偶尔洗一洗
- What's your problem? - What's my problem?
-你怎么回事  -我怎么回事
Yes, what's your problem?
是啊  你怎么回事
What's my problem? Dude, it's 2:00 a.M.
我怎么回事  现在是凌晨两点
- and all the lights are still on! - Hey, guys.
-灯还开着呢  -孩子们
What in the name of God could you possibly
上帝啊  都这个时候了
be fighting about right now?
你们有什么可以吵的
- He threw a football at my face. - He keeps waking me up.
-他用球砸我的脸  -他不让我睡觉
And I need to get sleep because I have a big game tomorrow.
我得睡觉  因为我明天有场重要比赛
Okay, Kevin, but Randall has a lot of homework,
好吧  凯文  可是兰德尔有很多作业
and now that he's on the football team,
而且他现在又加入了橄榄球队
he has a lot less time do do it.
所以他没多少时间写作业了
And why does he suddenly need to be on the football team?
他为什么突然要加入橄榄球队
What do I have to do with you guys?
我该拿你们怎么办
Do I have to make you go sleep in separate rooms?
难道非得让你们睡在不同房间吗
- Yes, actually that'd be great. - You don't have to do that...
-那样其实挺好的  -不用非得那样
Okay, that won't work
根本办不到
because the only empty room in the house
因为家里唯一一个空房间
- is the basement. - I want it.
-是地下室  -我过去
Kevin...
凯文
K... would you relax?
凯...  冷静一下好吗
Hey. Dude, come on.
兄弟  别这样
You don't have to go into the basement.
你不用非得去地下室
I'll turn off my light,
我会把灯关上
and I'll do my homework in the kitchen.
然后去厨房写作业
That's a very nice offer.
这个提议很不错
Kevin, do you hear what your brother's saying?
凯文  听见你弟弟说什么了吗
Yeah, I heard him.
听见了
- Hi, Kevin! - Ashley.
-嗨  凯文  -艾希莉
That baby teething?
孩子长牙了吗
- You know it. - All right.
-你知道的  -好吧
Ni hao, Mr. Hwa.
你好  华先生
Keep working on that core.
加油练肌肉啊
- Hey. - What's up?
-嗨  -你好
Morning, gentlemen.
早上好  先生们
- Hey. - Good morning.
-嗨  -早上好
Look at this, I got six miles.
看啊  我跑了九千多米
- Good for you, buddy. - Yup.
-不错嘛  老兄  -没错
I did eight.
我跑了一万二
- Is William still asleep? - Yeah.
-威廉还在睡吗  -是啊
I feel like yesterday's chemo took a lot out of him.
我觉得昨天的化疗让他累坏了
Morning hugs!
早晨的抱抱
- Give me my morning hug. - No, gross!
-给我个早晨的拥抱  -不  你太脏了
Daddy, you're all sweaty.
爸爸  你浑身都是汗
All right, come on girls,
好了  孩子们抓紧时间
backpacks, lunches, car.
装好书包  午饭  上车
Let's go. I'll be right out.
走吧  我马上就出去
- Have a great day, beautifuls. - You too.
-祝你们一天愉快  小美女们  -你也是
- Daddy loves you. - Bye, Dad, love you.
-爸爸爱你们  -再见  爸爸  爱你
Bye, kiddos.
再见  孩子们
Hey, Kevin.
凯文
Did you see a yellow legal pad in my office?
你有没有在我办公室看见一本黄色的拍纸本
You mean my bedroom?
你是指我的卧室吗
Do I though?
"卧室"吗
All right, I am gonna grab a shower.
好吧  我去冲个澡
- Meet you at the office before dinner. - Yeah.
-晚饭前办公室见  -好的
Look, he and I are having dinner tonight,
我们今晚要一起吃晚餐
so you have a Kevin-free evening.
所以他今晚不在家
Just the two of you?
就你们俩吗
- Alone? - No, we're meeting our mother.
-单独吃饭  -不  我们要去见妈妈
Oh, okay.
好吧
Why?
怎么了
No, I just couldn't imagine you and Kevin hanging out.
没什么  我想象不出你和凯文在一起的画面
What do you... Well, the guy lives in our house, Beth,
你什么...  他就住在我们家  贝丝
we hang out all the time.
我们一直都在一起呢
Yeah, but you guys are never in the same room alone together.
是啊  可你俩从没单独待在在一个房间
Uh, we just went for a run together.
我们刚刚一起去跑步了
Together?
你俩一起
Really?
真的吗
So, what this mean, "really?"
这是什么语气  "真的吗"
圣经故事  该隐杀死弟弟亚伯
It didn't end well for Cain and Abel, baby,
该隐和亚伯的结局可不好  宝贝儿
that's all I'm saying.
我就是这意思
Well, we're not Cain and Abel.
我们不是该隐和亚伯
Well, they were much less repressed.
可不  他们受的约束少多了
But if we were Cain and Abel
不过就算我们是该隐和亚伯
I'd be Cain, right?
我也是该隐  对吧
'Cause he's the brother who won?
因为他赢了
All right.
你说了算
- I love you. - Love you.
-我爱你  -爱你
That was your fastest run yet.
此次跑步为目前最快速度
Damn right it was.
必须的
Damn right.
小样儿
当前卡路里摄入量
蛋白质  碳水化合物
蔬菜
水果
- I should pee. - You just peed.
-我应该尿完再称  -你刚刚才尿过
- Every ounce counts. - That's true.
-少一两是一两  -没错
And I'm crushing this weigh-in.
我要用称重结果碾压你们
Get it!
我懂
All right, Kate, are you ready?
好的  凯特  准备好了吗
- I am. - All right. Let's do this.
-准备好了  -好  我们开始吧
- Oh, will you hold this for me? - Yeah.
-能帮我拿下这个吗  -好
All right. Congratulations, lady.
好的  祝贺你  美女
You are down a pound and a quarter.
你减掉了一斤二两
A pound?
就一斤
Yeah, and a... and a quarter.
对  还多二两呢
And a quarter.
二两
Okay, I kill myself for weeks, and I'm down a pound?
我累死累活好几周  竟然只掉一斤
- And a quarter. - Right. Yeah.
-还多二两呢  -对  没错
It's working, all right?
还是有效果的  对吧
You got to keep going, though.
不过你还得继续运动
This is the tough part, but you got this.
这是最困难的阶段  可你做到了
Yeah.
是啊
Good job.
干得漂亮
Down. Down is great.
掉秤了  掉秤就是好事
- Thanks. - Nice work, nice work.
-谢谢  -很棒 真不错
- All right. - All right, Toby, you ready?
-好了  -托比  你准备好了吗
Yup. All right.
好了
Okay. Oh, wow.
看我的
You lost eight more pounds, mister.
你减了七斤多  帅哥
- Yeah. All right. - You know what that means?
-可不是吗  -你知道这代表什么吗
Hey, guys, guess who just met their month goal?
大家猜猜  谁达到了本月的减肥目标
This guy!
就是这位
Nice. Hey, yeah, Toby, do you mind if we take a victory pic?
真不错  托比  你愿意拍张获胜照吗
- Oh, no, no, that's not necessary. - No, of course it is.
-不  不  不用了  -当然要拍
- No, it's no biggie. - You hit your goal.
-不  没什么大不了  -你达到目标了啊
It's no biggie.
这没什么
No. You are no biggie... anymore.
不  是你不再是大块头了
- Yeah. - I'm proud of you, Toby.
-对  -我为你骄傲  托比
Go, give 'em what they want.
去拍吧  满足他们的要求
Okay, all right.
好吧  听你的
Uh, I'll do the...
我去拍...
- I'll do the victory photo. - Yes, let's do it.
-我去拍获胜照  -好的  来吧
All right, we're doing it. All right, guys, let's get in here.
好  要拍照了  大家伙儿  都过来
- Victory photo. - Come on, circle it up.
-拍获胜照  -来吧  大家集合
All right, one, two, three.
好的  一  二  三
- Cheese! - Cheese!
-茄子  -茄子
Super cute. Another one. Smile!
超可爱  再来一张  笑
Yes! Beautiful!
好了  真美
我们的生活
第一季  第七集
I want to make a big push on rising temp futures.
我打算力推升温期货
Some of our clients don't currently believe in science,
目前我们的一些客户不相信科学
but we'll have 'em watch
等钞票开始滚滚而来
美国副总统戈尔畅销书《难以忽视的真相》同名纪录片  反映全球变暖
an Al Gore documentary once the cash starts rolling in.
我们要让他们看看阿尔·戈尔的纪录片
Am I right, people?
我说的对吧  各位
Come on, guys, nothing? That was...
怎么  没话说吗  什么情况
Is that the Manny?
那个人是奶爸吗
Yup. That's the Manny.
没错  是他
- I'm early! - Right.
-我来早了  -是啊
I'll be right there.
我马上就来
You guys look sharp.
你们看起来好有型
I'll meet you in the... meet you in the office.
我等下...  去办公室见你
- Okay. - Cool.
-好啊  -好
Just chill out in your office?
我去你办公室歇会儿
Yeah.
好
That is the Manny.
这位就是奶爸
*Straighten up and fly right*
*改过自新吧  向前飞翔*
*Straighten up and stay right*
*改过自新吧  好好生活*
*Straighten up and fly right*
*改过自新吧  向前飞翔*
*Cool down, Papa, don't you blow your top*
*冷静点爸爸  不要发脾气*
Sounds good.
唱得真好听
- Really? - Yeah.
-真的吗  -当然
I don't remember the last time I was this nervous.
我都不记得上次这么紧张是什么时候了
Oh, it's just rehearsal, right?
只是排练而已  对吧
Yeah, but it's my first rehearsal in ten years.
对  可这是我十年来第一次排练
You're gonna do great, babe.
你会演得很棒  宝贝儿
what are you planning on wearing to the boy's game tonight?
今晚儿子们比赛  你打算穿什么
Because I know we usually wear Kevin's colors,
因为我们通常穿凯文队的颜色
but now that Randall's playing for another school...
可现在兰德尔代表另一个学校参赛
The game. Crap.
比赛  糟了
I'm meeting Bob Parrish tonight
今晚我要跟鲍勃·帕里什见面
to close the Doylestown deal.
完成多伊尔斯敦的交易
- Doylestown? - Yeah.
-多伊尔斯敦  -对
Really? So you got it?
真的吗  你拿到这笔交易了
I-I told you last week.
我...  我上周告诉过你
Well, I'm sure I would have remembered if you said that.
你要是说过我肯定记得
- Oh, I know that I did. - Okay, well,
-我确实说过  -好吧  那...
is there any way that you can move the meeting
你能不能换个时间见面
because that coach is coming to scout Kevin?
因为教练会来物色球员
It's a really big game for him.
这场比赛对凯文非常重要
It's a big day for me, too, and a big day for you.
今天对我也很重要  对你也重要
And a big day for Kevin, so...
对凯文也重要  所以...
I'll see what I can do.
让我想想办法
- Okay. - Okay.
-好吧  -好
Jack?
杰克
Yeah.
什么事
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起  我错了
I'm all over the place.
我脑子里都乱成一团了
- Have a good day. - Have fun.
-要开心哦  -你也是
Thanks.
谢谢
No, of course.
不  当然
I totally understand. We can do dinner another time.
我完全理解  我们可以下次一起做晚餐
That was Mom? She's not coming?
是妈妈吗  她不来了吗
- Yeah. - What'd she say?
-是  -她怎么说
Well, tell Miguel I hope he feels better soon.
转告米格尔  我希望他早日康复
Let me talk to her. Is Miguel sick?
让我跟她说  米格尔病了吗
Let me just talk to her.
让我跟她说
Just give me the phone.
把电话给我
- Yeah, I'll tell Kevin. - Just put her on speaker.
-好  我会告诉凯文  -打开免提
We can reschedule.
我们再安排时间
Just let me talk to her before you go.
挂电话前让我和她说几句
- Love you, too. - Before she...
-我也爱你  -她挂电话之前...
- Bye. - Let me talk to her for...
-拜拜  -让我和她说...
It's Miguel's gout.
米格尔的痛风犯了
Really? I didn't know they made gout anymore.
是吗  我之前以为他们不会再得痛风了
- So she's not coming then? - No.
-那她不来了吗  -是的
- Not coming. - Oh, okay.
-不来了  -好的
- It's the two of us. - Yes.
-那就是我们两个了  -没错
Yeah. I mean, if you got work to do though,
如果你还有工作要做
I... we don't have to go.
那我们不用去
- No! I'm, I'm okay. - You're all right?
-不  我没事  -你确定
Yeah. Uh, if you've got lines to learn
是的  如果你有台词要背
or something, then we can...
或者其他事  我们可以...
I'm good. I'm up to speed, so...
没事  我都背好了
You and me.
你和我
You and I.
Hey, girls, wash up and come down.
姑娘们  洗好手下来吧
So, Kevin and Randall are out tonight.
今晚凯文和兰德尔出去了
It'll just be you and us ladies.
只剩你和我们这几个姑娘了
Nothing for me, thanks.
不用给我  谢谢
You know, my dad had cancer.
我爸爸之前得了癌症
Lung.
肺癌
I didn't want to say anything 'cause, you know,
我以前什么都不想说  因为
it wasn't exactly a happy ending for him.
他最后的结局并不算完美
Endings rarely are.
结局很少会是完美的
Weed helped.
大麻会有帮助
With the appetite, you know? But...
有助于开胃  但...
I just figured with your history,
我才了解了你的过去
I didn't want to bring that up because of...
我不想提起这个  因为
Marijuana doesn't have the same kind of trigger.
大麻和那些效果不一样
Even my doctor said.
我的医生也这么说
Can't have you going out in the night
我不能让你为了我
scoring drugs on my account.
大晚上出去买毒品
What... what if I was to tell you I had a little stash?
如果我告诉你我有一些存货呢
Then I'd say, woman, you surprise me.
那我会说  女士  你让我大吃一惊
And I'm not easily surprised.
而我很少大吃一惊的
How about I feed the girls, right?
我先让姑娘们吃饭  好吗
Get their asses in bed,
安顿好她们睡觉
and bake us up some special brownies.
再给我们烤一点特制布朗尼蛋糕吃
- I like that plan. - You like that?
-这提议不错  -是吧
Right.
就这么定了
Hey! How are you?
你好吗
- What do you think? This place is great, right? - Yeah.
-怎么样  这地儿不错吧  -是的
Yeah. The last time I was here, I bro'ed out with Mario Lopez.
我上次来这儿  是和马里奥·洛佩兹一起的
I don't know who that is.
不知道那是谁
Oh, okay.
好吧
Oh, my God. We love you.
天呐  我们超喜欢你的
Yeah? All right, well, cool. Let's, uh... do a selfie.
是吗  酷  我们来张自拍吧
- Give it to me, I'll take it. - No, no, it's a selfie.
-给我吧  我来拍  -不  是自拍
- It's a thing.  -Right. Got it.
-就是自己拍  -明白了
That's gonna turn out great.
这张会蛮不错的
- Thank you. - I'm suddenly getting why we came here.
-谢谢  -我突然明白我们为啥来这了
What'd you say?
你说什么
I said I'm su...
我说我突...
- It's a great place! - Yeah!
-这地方真棒  -是啊
You're... Oh, you got to walk around.
你从那边转过去吧吧
Yeah, yeah!
好的
Big table.
桌子比较大
He's never been here.
他从没来过这里
There he is!
来了啊
Hey, everybody.
大家好
Hey, guys.
大伙们
All right.
好
So, he's got a piece of egg salad sandwich
他胡子上挂着
dangling from his moustache,
一块鸡蛋沙拉三明治
riding me about how
还嘲弄我
I don't take my job seriously.
对待工作有多不认真
Eventually, I just had to walk out while he was talking.
最后  我在他还说着话的时候直接走人了
Jack.
杰克
I forgot to kiss Rebecca good-bye this morning.
我今早忘记跟丽贝卡吻别了
First time in 15 years.
15年来第一次
- Knock, knock. - Hey, Heather.
-咚咚咚  -海瑟
Sabatino's?
萨巴蒂诺家的吗
Best in the city.
城里最好吃的
Please, I can make a better meatball sub
拜托  我做的肉丸三明治
than that, blindfolded.
可比这一团东西好吃多了
Is that an offer?
这算是邀请吗
- I need you to sign off on these. - Okay.
-这些需要签字  -好的
Do you have a...
你有...
- Here you go. - Thanks. Thanks, Jack.
-给你  -谢谢  杰克
Here...
这里...
- There you go. - And... you missed one.
-给你  -你漏了一处
What would I do without you?
没有你我可怎么办
There you go.
给你
- Thank you. - Okay.
-谢谢  -不客气
What?
怎么了
I was playing... Are you...
我只是在闹着玩  你...
Took your pen.
拿了你的笔
Thanks.
谢谢
Your wife should've got that.
你老婆应该帮你整理好的
Thank you.
谢谢
Just...
别闹...
Hi. I'm so sorry I'm late.
抱歉我迟到了
Hey, no, you're not late.
你没有迟到
Oh... Oh, my goodness!
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
天呐
It's been too long.
太久没见了
Guys, this is...
大伙们  这位是
- Rebecca Malone. - Um... it's Pearson now.
-丽贝卡·马隆  -现在改姓皮尔森了
- Oh. Right. - But, hi, hi, Rebecca.
-是啊  -大家好  我是丽贝卡
Hi, nice to meet you. Hi.
见到你很高兴
Thank you so much for thinking of me for this. It really...
为我想到这些真贴心  真是太...
- it means a lot. - Are you kidding?
-意义重大  -开玩笑吗
Our manager decided we needed a female vocalist
我们的经理决定请一位女歌手
and I told him it's... it's got to be the girl
我告诉他  必须得是那个
I used to play the keys for.
我为她弹过琴的姑娘
Well, I guess you forgot this girl you used to play keys for
我猜你忘了那姑娘已经
- got old. - Not from where I'm standing.
-老了  -我觉得可不是
- Really? - Yeah. Yeah.
-真的吗  -真的
- Hey, what do you... you want to jump in? - Yeah.
-准备好了吗  -是的
Yeah, I'm ready. Okay.
准备好了
One, two,
一  二
one, two, three.
一  二  三
*A buzzard took a monkey for a ride in the air*
*秃鹰带着猴子在空中翱翔*
*Monkey thought that everything was on the square*
*猴子觉得万物都是公平的*
*The buzzard tried to throw the monkey off his back*
*秃鹰想把猴子从背上丢下去*
*The monkey grabbed his neck and said, now, listen, Jack*
*猴子抓着他的脖子说  给我听着  杰克*
*Straighten up and fly right*
*改过自新吧  向前飞翔*
*Straighten up and stay right...*
*改过自新吧  好好生活*
Hey, you've reached Toby, I can't take your call right now
我是托比  我现在无法接听您的电话
'cause I'm out saving the world from evil,
因为我出去拯救世界了
or it's Tuesday, and I'm bowling.
或者今天周二  我去打保龄球了
Toby out.
说完了
Hey, it's me.
是我
Again.
又打来了
I just...
我只是...
wanted to apologize for ducking out of the meeting. Again.
想为我又一次从互助会溜走  向你道个歉
Well, not like I've ducked out of previous meetings, I'm...
并不是说我之前也偷溜过  我...
Please call me.
给我回电话吧
This is...not expected.
这...  这有点意外啊
I know you're mad at me,
我知道你在生我气
and I get it. I should have handled myself better.
我也理解  我本该控制好自己的情绪
No, no, no. No, it's fine, it's fine.
不  不不不  没事  没关系的
I literally just saw that you called.
我只是刚看到你的来电
I've just, I've... I've been busy, is all.
只不过...  我最近挺忙的  仅此而已
Okay. Good. Yeah.
好吧  那就好
Can I come in?
我可以进去吗
Uh... uh, yep.
可以啊
Yeah. Come on in.
当然  进来吧
It's the maid's day off.
今天女佣请假了
You binged?
你在暴饮暴食啊
No! What?
没有  哪儿有
This is no big deal.
这不算什么啦
I just, I hit a goal and I celebrated
我达成目标了  庆祝一下
by eating some food that I actually like the taste of.
吃点我真正爱吃的东西而已
You know, I don't... I don't have an eating problem.
我又没有  没有饮食问题
Yeah. Well, you didn't have a problem
你狂吃掉这些东西
eating all this food.
倒是没啥问题
- All right, that's fair. - Listen, Toby.
-好吧  说的也对  -托比
We can just get back on our program,
我们仍然可以恢复节食计划
like, right now.
就现在
Here's the thing.
是这样的
Depriving myself,
克制自己的饮食
uh... makes me absolutely nuts.
快要把我逼疯了
So, I think I'm gonna need to loosen the reins a little bit.
所以我需要稍微释放下
What does that mean, loosen the reins?
稍微释放下  什么意思
That means...
意思就是
I'm done dieting, Kate.
我决定不节食了  凯特
But I still support you 100%.
不过我还是会全力支持你的
How?
怎么支持
Like, we were supposed to do this together?
比如说我们之前约好一起节食吗
Or like, I agreed to go out with you
或者  我同意和你约会
because you were gonna lose the weight for me.
就因为你曾经想为了我减肥
And... and I did.
我的确减了
I lost some of the weight.
减掉了些
And if I gain it back, I will lose it again.
如果它反弹了  我还会再把它减掉的
All right? You are not alone in this.
好吗  你不是一个人在坚持
When we are together,
我们在一块儿时
I will eat the way that you eat.
你吃什么  我也吃什么
I swear. I swear on this bag of Cool Ranch...
我发誓  我以这袋垃圾食品的名义发誓
which is...
其实它
way more disgusting than I remembered, by the way.
这东西比我印象中的难吃多了
I just don't know how this is gonna work.
我不明白这样子怎么行得通
Then I'll show you.
我会让你看到的
All right? Tonight.
好吗  就今晚
We'll go to dinner.
我们一起吃饭
We will eat sensibly, hmm?
一起合理饮食
We will talk as always.
如往常一样聊天
We will laugh as always,
如往常一样欢笑
all right? We'll still be us, I promise.
行吗  我保证  我们之间什么都不会变
Okay?
好吗
Hey, congrats.
恭喜
Heard you got your own room.
听说你有属于自己的房间了
Yeah.
是啊
What's up with you?
你怎么了
Nothing.
没事
Randall.
兰德尔
Why does he hate me so much?
他怎么就那么讨厌我呢
Kevin doesn't hate you.
凯文不是讨厌你
You guys are just so intense with each other, you know?
你们俩只是太爱跟彼此较劲了  知道吗
Try lightening things up a little.
试着放轻松点
Joke around with him more.
跟他多开开玩笑
You know Mom is gonna kill you if she sees you
你知道老妈要是看到你化成这样
putting on all that makeup, right?
会杀了你的吧
Pop-Tarts and Yoo-hoo.
果馅饼和饼干
Breakfast of champions.
冠军专用早餐
What do you want?
你来干嘛
I just came to see your dungeon.
我来参观下你的地下城
I mean, your digs.
你的房间
I think it's cool.
我觉得这儿很酷
Yeah... totally.
是啊  的确
In a couple days you won't notice
这段时间你还不会注意到
that funky mildew, and the asbestos.
那发臭的霉菌  还有防火布
I'd give it at least a year till it's imbedded in your lungs.
我打赌还要至少再过一年你才会吸进肺里
Randall, can you please just get out of here, man?
兰德尔  你能走开吗  兄弟
Look, I came down here to get away from you.
我来这儿就是不想看到你
Dude, I was just joking.
兄弟  我就开个玩笑啦
Are you deaf?
你是聋了吗
I said get out.
我叫你走啊
Get a life.
别这么可悲
You feeling anything yet?
你有感觉了吗
I...
我
...was I supposed to eat a quarter of the brownie,
我是该吃掉四分之一的蛋糕
or a quarter of the pan?
还是四分之一的锅
Yes, definitely.
当然了
What? What's so funny?
笑什么  什么这么好笑
That's not the answer. It's not...
不是这么回答的  不是
You did it right.
你做得对
You ate it.
你把它吃了
Shh, don't laugh so loud.
别笑得这么大声
I don't want to wake up the girls, okay?
别把孩子们吵醒了  好吗
I knew I smelled chocolate.
我就说我闻到了巧克力的味道
Why are you guys eating brownies in the basement?
你们为什么在地下室吃蛋糕
- Can I have one? - No.
-我可以吃一块吗  -不行
These are adult brownies.
这是大人吃的蛋糕
These are work brownies.
这是工作食用的蛋糕
Shut up.
别笑了
Tomorrow, I'm gonna make you some kid's brownies, okay?
明天我给你做儿童蛋糕吃  好吗
- Okay. - All right. Go ahead back upstairs. Go to bed.
-好吧  -好了  上楼睡觉去吧
And be gentle getting back in that bed. I don't want you
回床上动作轻点
- to wake up your sister, okay? - All right.
-别把你妹妹吵醒了  好吗  -好
- Okay. Good night. - Night.
-好了  晚安  -晚安
- Good night.
-晚安
- You... - Was she walking or was she floating?
-你... -她是在走路还是在梦游
I feel bad they have to crowd themselves on my account.
我很抱歉她们俩因为我要挤在一间房里
I know Annie must be wanting her room back.
我知道安妮一定想回她的房间
You're not the one who's cramping anybody's style in this house.
你并不是那个给这家里添堵的人
- Okay. - My office used to be my haven.
-好吧  -办公室曾是我的天堂
Now, it's Kevin's hamper.
现在却成了凯文的食篮
Yes.
没错
I wish he would leave.
我真希望他早点走人
Compliments of the owner.
店主送的
Thank you very much, appreciate that.
谢谢  非常感谢
See? Don't I get the hookup or what?
你瞧  哥是不是处处惹人爱
I haven't done so bad for myself, right?
我混得还是不错的吧
You're the mayor of free shrimp.
你是免费甜虾市长
All right, so, how's the play going?
言归正传  你戏演得怎么样
The play.
你的戏
- It's good. - See you still working it, Pearson.
-挺好的  -看你过得还不错嘛  皮尔森
Donny frickin' Watson. What's up, man, how you doing?
唐尼·沃森  兄弟  最近怎样啊
- I'm good, I'm good. - Yeah?
-我很好  很好  -是吗
Oh, man, I can't stay. I got to take my girl to see Cats.
兄弟  我得走了  带我女儿去看《猫》
她在高中还扮演过葛丽兹贝拉She even played Grizabella in high school.
音乐剧《猫》中过气的魅力猫
It's a whole thing but...
非去不可  不过...
let's connect soon, yeah?
我们再联系  好吗
All right, yeah, yeah, yeah, I'd like that very much.
好啊  好啊  一定联系
I'd like that very much. You're looking good.
一定联系  你看起来相当不错
Donny Watson.
唐尼·沃森
How you guys know each other?
你们怎么认识的
Funny.
真好笑
What, are you serious?
怎么  你真不知道吗
- Yeah. - He...
-是啊  -他...
played my best friend on The Manny.
在《靓男保姆》里扮演我的好友
- Out of context... - Yeah.
-这下想起来了吧  -是啊
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - I must have missed that episode.
-没错  没错  -我一定错过那集了
He was a series regular, actually, on the show.
其实  他是那部剧的常驻演员
For four years, he was a series regular.
四年来  一直都是常驻演员
Have you ever seen my show?
你有看过我的电视剧吗
- Of course I have. - Yeah?
-我当然看过  -真的吗
Yeah.
真的
What was my, uh, what was my character's name?
那么  我扮演的角色叫什么名字
Don't tell him.
别告诉他
What was my character's name on the show?
我剧中角色的名字是什么
Okay.
好吧
- Kevin. - No, no, man, it's all right.
-凯文  -不不  兄弟  没事
- Just finish the dinner, man. - It's all right,
-至少把晚饭吃完  -没关系
it's all right, it's all right.
真的  没关系
Good talk.
聊得很愉快
And so this, uh, dog
这只...  狗狗
just keeps getting reincarnated.
一直不停地转世投胎
And so, and so, it's like he... I think he's a schna...
还有...  我觉得它可能是
like a schnauzer, like, poodle mix
雪纳瑞犬和贵宾犬的杂交品种
and he's running around town trying to solve crimes,
它在小镇上四处溜达侦破案件
but he keeps getting hit by cars.
但总被汽车撞
- May I?  - Yeah, yeah, thank you.
-可以收了吗  -可以  谢谢
And did you see what happened here?
你看到了吗
You had chicken. I had the chicken.
你吃的是鸡肉  我也吃的鸡肉
- We are in this together. - Thank you.
-我们一起共同努力  -谢谢
Would you two like to see our dessert tray?
两位想看看我们的甜点吗
Uh, no, thank you.
不了  谢谢
- Walk away, fine sir. - Aright.
-走开  老兄  -好的
Hey, wait.
等一下
- He'll have a look. - I will?
-他会看一眼  -我会吗
Dude, I know you want it,
老兄  我知道你想吃
and if you don't have it here,
就算你没有在这吃
you're gonna go home, you're gonna stuff your face
等回家后  你也一定会胡吃海塞
and you're gonna lie to me about it.
然后骗我说你没吃
You'll have a full-on food mistress and I...
你会在金屋藏个甜点小三  而我...
But I will never love her the way that I love you.
但我对她的爱绝对不及你
This is not a joke.
别开玩笑了
- I'm being serious. - Okay, all right, okay, okay.
-我是认真的  -好吧  好吧
How are we gonna make this relationship work
如果我们彼此之间还有所隐瞒
if we're gonna keep things from each other?
那我们的关系该如何维系呢
I'll just have to handle it.
我必须得解决这事
- All right. - Okay.
-好吧  -好的
- Hold both at the same time. - You made it.
-同时拿着两个  -你真搞到了
What's with, uh, all the beige?
你怎么穿一身米色衣服
I'm trying to remain neutral.
我想保持中立
- Yeah? Okay. - Yeah.
-是吗  好吧  -没错
Wait, where's Kevin?
等等  凯文在哪
There he is.
他在那
- Twelve. - Twelve.
-12号  -12号
Down, set, hut.
预备  开球
Thank you.
谢谢
Now, let's go, McKinley Wildcats.
现在  加油  麦金利野猫队
Rehearsal? Rehearsal was good?
彩排呢  你彩排还成功吗
Oh, Jack, honestly, it was amazing.
杰克  说实话真的棒极了
- Yeah? - Yeah,
-真的吗  -是啊
just being on stage again,
重新站上舞台唱歌
and singing and I missed it.
我真是太怀念了
- Yeah. - The smell of the microphone alone was...
-好的  -那麦克风的气味...
- The microphone has a smell? - Hey, Jack!
-麦克风也有气味吗  -你好  杰克
Big game for Kevin, huh?
凯文的大比赛是吧
Yeah, and with your Bobby
没错  有你家鲍比
opening up holes in the backfield,
在后场防守支援
Kevin's not gonna have to do a whole lot.
凯文估计不需要费太大力气
All right, folks, McKinley Middle School has possession
好了  各位  由麦金利中学队首先进攻
with visiting Hanes Academy on defense.
来访海恩斯学院的防守
You can finish telling me the rest later.
等结束后  你再告诉我彩排的事
Down.
准备
Set... hut!
预备  开球
Blue 22!
蓝队22号
Blue 42!
蓝色42号
Get down, set!
预备
Hut!
开球
- Go, go, go, go! - Go, go, go, go, go!
-快  快跑  -快  快跑
What are they doing?
他们怎么回事
All right, all right.
好了  好了
Boys!
孩子们
Hey. Hey, come on, Kev. Would you stop?
拜托  小凯  停一下
No, it's all right, Randall. I'm just gonna go back to my hotel.
没事  兰德尔  我要回酒店了
Leave me alone, all right?
别管我好吗
Hey, I'll give you a thousand dollars right now
如果现在你能说出来我是干什么的
if you can tell me what I do for a living.
我就给你一千美元
- Uh, you're a Wall Street guy, right? - Yeah.
-你不就是在华尔街上班的嘛  -是吗
- Yeah. - Okay, but what does that mean?
-是啊  -那又意味着什么
Uh, you know, you do the-the... the... like, The Big Short.
就是...  做那种"大空头"
You do the Ponzu schemes.
搞"柚子骗局"的
Oh, dude, it's ponzu sauce, Ponzi schemes. Whatever.
伙计  是柚子醋  庞氏骗局  算了
Look, the point is, you don't know what I do, and that's fine.
重点在于你不明白我的工作  这没关系
What difference does it make if I didn't watch The Manny?
这和我没看过《靓男保姆》有什么区别
You hated the show! You were so ashamed of it, you quit.
你讨厌那部剧  你觉得可耻  所以退出了
Not at first. At first, I was proud of that show, Randall.
一开始没有  本来我挺骄傲的  兰德尔
And I invited every single one of you to tapings.
我请你们每个人来看录像
Kate's the only one that came.
只有凯特一个人来了
Well, she had to. You were paying her.
她没办法  你付钱给她的
Come on, dude. That was funny.
笑一下  挺搞笑的
What are you...?
你在看什么...
《靓男保姆》
Now that... that is funny.
现在才叫搞笑
That's great.
好极了
Replaced by another black man.
又被一个黑人替代了
What the hell did you just say?
你刚刚说什么
No. "Replaced by another black man."
你说"又被一个黑人替代了"
Hey, you tell me what that means.
告诉我你什么意思
Don't worry about it, Randall.
没什么意思  兰德尔
No. Please, Kevin. Let's hear it, right?
得了  凯文  说来听听
What are you harboring?
你言下之意是什么
'Cause God knows I would really love to hear this.
天晓得我有多想听听
You always got special treatment.
你总能获得特别待遇
Because I'm black?
因为我是黑人吗
No, because you're black and you're adopted.
不  因为你是黑人  而且是养子
Oh, yeah, hit the jackpot with that combination.
是啊  这个组合真让我中了头彩
- Couldn't have had it any easier. - In our house, you did.
-真是太容易了  -在我们家  就是这样
- With our mother, you did. - Oh, right.
-在妈妈那儿也是  -好吧
- Okay, here we go. - Why can't you just admit it, man?
-继续说啊  -你就承认吧
- Admit what? - Just admit that you were more important to her,
-承认什么  -就承认她更看重你
and that she wanted to make sure
每一天  每一分钟
that you felt special every single minute of every single day
她都要确保你感觉自己是特别的
so that, yeah, you wouldn't feel like the odd man out.
这样你就不会觉得自己受排挤
Well, gee, Kevin, I wonder why
凯文  我倒想知道
she was worried about me feeling that way?
她为什么会担心我有那种感觉呢
What the hell does that mean?
你是什么意思
- Just go back to your hotel. - No. No, hold on.
-回你的酒店去吧  -不  等等
Randall, hold... No. What does that mean?
兰德尔  等等...  你是什么意思
It means you treated me like a dog.
意思是你把我当狗一样
And just like a dog, I kept coming back again and again,
我就像狗一样一次次地回来
just hoping for a scrap from you,
期望从你那儿得到一些残渣
like a crumb of affection or kindness or respect.
得到一丁点儿喜欢  善意或者尊重
- Respect? You wanted my respect? - Yeah.
-尊重  你想要我尊重你  -对
Yeah, okay. No, you wanted to show me up, Randall.
不  你只想在我面前炫耀  兰德尔
Which is what you did every single chance you got.
只要一有机会就如此
- No, I did not. - You showed me up!
-我没有  -你出我洋相
I'm done with this conversation.
我不想跟你谈这个话题了
Done with this conversation? In any other family,
不想谈了吗  换在其他家庭
I would have been the star!
我就会是个明星
Yeah, you know what, bro? You're no star. That is a star.
知道吗  你才不是什么明星  那才叫明星
- Get your hands off me. - Get your hands off me.
-把你手拿开  -把你手拿开
You don't push my body.
不许推我
- Don't touch me, okay? - Don't touch me.
-别碰我  -别碰我
- What is wrong with you? - What is wrong with you?
-你有什么毛病  -你有什么毛病
Oh, my God. Don't put your hands on my body.
老天  别用你的手碰我
Is that... is that the Manny?
那是...那是"奶爸"吗
Ow! My face...
我的脸...
Kevin? Hey, Kevin?
凯文  凯文
You're all right, man?
你没事吧
Do you... want me to call someone?
需要我...打电话给谁吗
Oh. Oh, it's, uh...
这是...
No.
不用
This is my brother.
这是我弟弟
Oh. Hey, man.
你好  哥们
Hey, Seth Meyers.
你好  塞斯·梅耶斯
- Okay. - Yeah.
-没事吗  -是啊
No. You know what? Let's go.
怎么着  我们走吧
I'm still black. Come on, let's go.
我还是黑人  走吧
Let's get the hell out of here.
快离开这儿
I'm sorry I couldn't help more with moving the heavy stuff.
抱歉没能帮你搬那个大家伙
That's okay.
没事
Did you know I grew up in a house with 14 people in it?
知道吗  我在一个住着十四人的家里长大的
My parents, four siblings,
我父母  四个兄弟姐妹
aunts, cousins,
阿姨  表亲
three bedrooms.
有三个卧室
- How many bathrooms? - One.
-有多少卫生间  -一间
Oh, my gosh,
天啊
when I was young, all I did was dream of living alone.
从小我就梦想着能自己住
Like some hippie life, you know?
像嬉皮士那样生活
Like in some artist loft downtown.
住在市中心的艺术家楼廊里
No husband.
没有丈夫
Definitely no kids.
当然也没有孩子
So what happened?
后来发生了什么
I met your damn son.
我遇见了你可恶的儿子
One look in his eyes,
一看到他的眼睛
he ruined everything.
就把我所有梦想都毁了
Me, I pretty much always lived alone.
我可是一个人住了大半辈子
Now I have Randall.
现在有了兰德尔
And you.
还有你
And the girls
还有孩子们
to fall asleep to, wake up to every day.
陪她们送走和迎来每一天
I hope that's a good thing.
希望这是件好事
Mostly.
大部分是
Makes me feel sad to die.
让我都不想死了
I love it when there's a new moon like this.
我喜欢这样的新月
Splendid against the night, the searchlights...
在夜空中熠熠生辉  那些探照灯
the tracers' arcs, and the red flare of bombs.
那些闪耀的弧线  红色的照明弹
How do you know that?
你怎么知道这句话的
It's in this book of poems
一本诗集中看到的
that Randall's had since he was a baby.
是兰德尔小时候的一本诗集
Oh, yeah, that's right.
是啊  对啊
The one I gave Rebecca back in the day.
我以前给丽贝卡的那本
What?
什么
- What'd you say? - I'm feeling a little tired,
-你说什么  -我有点累了
Beth, I think I'll...
贝丝  我还是...
Hell no, you ain't cancering your way out of this one, old man.
不行  这事别想拿癌症当挡箭牌  老头子
- Beth... -You better talk.
-贝丝  -你最好讲明白
Get your asses in the car.
赶紧上车
We're gonna talk big-time at home.
我们回家得好好谈谈
You're right.
你说得对
Mom did favor me.
咱妈确实偏爱我
She did.
她确实是
Showered me with attention.
特别关注我
Took my side more often than not.
总是向着我
And I ate every bit of her love up.
我将她的爱全部"吃"进心里了
Ate it up like Pac-Man.
就像吃豆小精灵那样
You know why?
你知道为什么吗
Because the one person I wanted it from the mo...
因为我最想得到爱的那个人...
You know, back there with those people,
刚才跟那些人在一起时
it's the first time in 36 years
36年来  第一次
you've said the words, "He's my brother."
你说了那句话  "他是我弟弟"
Come on, Randall, that can't be...
兰德尔  那不是...
Claiming me.
对外宣称
My brother.
我的弟弟
Well, then, that really sucks.
那真够糟糕的
Rebecca has known who you were for Randall's entire life?
丽贝卡在兰德尔小时候就知道你的存在吗
Yes, that's right.
对  没错
And she never told him?
她从没告诉他吗
- I don't know, Beth. - Lied to him, when he asked.
-我不知道  贝丝  -他问起  就骗他
- I got to tell him. - No. No, no, no, no.
-我得告诉他  -不不不
Beth, you can't do that.
贝丝  你不能那么做
Oh, "Beth you can't do that"?
什么叫"贝丝  你不能那么做"
This is my husband.
那是我的丈夫
This is my marriage.
这是我的婚姻
I know, but the closeness he has with his mom,
我知道  他跟他妈妈感情那么好
you tell him this, it'll destroy it.
你告诉他  只会破坏那份感情
Whoa, someone's high.
有人嗑嗨了啊
Good night.
晚安
- Night. - Good night.
-晚安  -晚安
You and my wife got high together?
你跟我老婆一起嗑嗨了吗
That's pretty cool.
挺不错的
Good for you.
真不错
All right, I'm gonna head up to bed.
好了  我要去睡觉了
Not that way; she moved you.
不是那边  她给你换地方了
What do you mean, she moved me? She moved me where?
什么叫给我换地方了  换哪儿了
Oh, back in the basement.
又住回地下室了
- No, we'll move you back upstairs. - No, come-- hey, listen.
-再让你搬回楼上  -不用  听我说
I should be getting out of your hair soon anyway.
反正我也住不了多久
You know, until then, this is actually a pretty sweet set-up.
离开之前  在这里睡挺好的
There's no bathroom down here.
这里没有卫生间
I can walk a flight of stairs.
走几层楼梯而已
Well, uh...
好吧...
It's been a day.
折腾了一天
Yeah.
是啊
Night.
晚安
Hey, uh, Randall.
兰德尔
Uh, do you want to...
你想...
Do you want to hang out down here for little bit with me?
你想在这里跟我待一会儿吗
We could, uh, turn the TV on or something.
我们可以看会儿电视什么的
For a little while.
就一会儿
- Yeah? - Why not?
-对  -好啊
- Cool. - Yeah.
-很棒  -是
Uh, Rebecca, this is Beth.
丽贝卡  我是贝丝
Yeah, um, so William just told me something really interesting
威廉刚刚跟我说了一件有意思的事
about the two of you.
关于你们俩的
So, yeah, I'm gonna need you to call me back, okay?
所以你要给我回电  好吗
Right away.
马上回电
As soon as you get this message.
收到留言后  就立刻回电
Okay, bye.
好了  再见
Manny's gonna buy you a mockingbird.
奶爸会给你买只"知更鸟"
You hate me, don't you?
你讨厌我  是吧
You want me to open up that big bottle of wine
你想让我打开那瓶
you've been saving for ten years.
你保存了十年的佳酿吗
Manny say, "What?!"
宝贝说啥哟
Hey, you never finished telling me about your rehearsal.
你还没说完你彩排的事情
It's okay; I'm tired.
不说了  我累了
We can talk about it tomorrow.
我们可以明天再说
Okay.
好
Hey, can you turn the light out, babe?
你能把灯关了吗  亲爱的
I just realized we didn't eat dinner tonight, Jack.
我刚意识到我们今晚都没吃晚餐  杰克
I had a pretty big lunch; I'm good.
我中午吃得很饱  晚饭不用吃了
Well, I'm gonna go make myself something then.
那我自己去弄点吃的
The light, babe.
关灯  亲爱的
Mom!
妈妈
What?
怎么了
I can't turn the washing machine off.
我关不掉洗衣机了
I think it's possessed.
我觉得它着魔了
Kev, you know you can always
小凯  你可以随时搬回去
go back to your old room with Randall.
跟兰德尔一起住
Oh, my God.
天呐
This is the best washing machine in the whole world.
这是全世界最好的洗衣机
I'm actually,
说真的
I'm turned on by this washing machine.
这台洗衣机真让我兴奋
Well, I can show you turned on.
我来告诉你什么叫"性奋"
Jack, help.
杰克  快来帮忙
It's leaking everywhere!
水漏得到处都是
Kids, get the buckets.
孩子们  拿水桶
Okay.
好了
This is bail out!
拯救大行动啊
Okay, kids.
好了  孩子们
Washing machine is officially cooked, baby.
洗衣机这下真是不行了  亲爱的
Nah, she's still got some life in her.
不  她还能用呢
At least six more cycles.
至少还能洗六轮
Jack, we have three infants.
杰克  我们家有三个孩子
We're going to be doing six cycles by noon.
中午之前就能洗六回了
We can do it. You wash and I'll fold.
我们自己来  你来洗  我来叠
Baby, one day, I'm gonna buy you
亲爱的  总有一天
the best washing machine in the world.
我会给你买台世上最好的洗衣机
原创翻译  双语字幕
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译:  moonshine7   小萝莉    Tracy-旋子
翻译:   桑葚    小泡椒   兔牙Bobby猫
校对:  红枫    不高兴童鞋
时间轴:  贝壳   ccisoda
后期:  AppleXue    总监： 红枫Gabriel
一键收藏网盘资源生活大爆炸 吸血鬼日记
西部世界 谍网 超女
美剧资源应有尽有
扫码即刻关注
Zimuzu特别推荐
马上关注微信人人美剧（rrmjapp）
第一时间下载无删减美剧  必须登录字幕组网站www.zimuzu.tv
www.zimuzu.tv  更好更快的原创翻译 双语字幕